Guide to the Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files 1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989) MS 3009-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files
1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989)
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 21
254 Linear feet in 178 record cartons and 62 flat boxes of various sizes
The Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files were assembled by the Time Inc. Archives and contain records from the advertising promotion and circulation promotion departments of many Time Inc. publications, including Fortune, Life, and Time.
Arrangement
The record group is organized alphabetically by magazine title (or similar category) in a single large series based on the Time Inc. Archive's original arrangement. Generally, each magazine title is further organized alphabetically by subject; such groups include Advertisers Lists, Advertising Promotion, Circulation Promotion, and Education Department. Arrangement within these groups varies across magazine titles. Materials may be organized alphabetically, or chronologically by year and alphabetically within each year, with general materials first.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials may include contracts and agreements, and files with personally identifiable information. Restricted materials are located in box R55. Unreformatted audiovisual material and digital material in the collection is not accessible. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Materials
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Additional Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion files can be found arranged by magazine title in the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1). Additional Time Education Department files can be found in the Time Inc. Time Publishing and Business Records (MS 3009-RG 24, Series VII).
Scope and Contents
The Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files represent the history of the company's two major revenue models: advertising sales and reader subscriptions. The record group was assembled by the Time Inc. Archives and incorporates material from many of the company's magazine titles. The files originated from a variety of departments across Time Inc., most notably the advertising promotion and circulation promotion departments, but also advertising sales, circulation, consumer marketing, and market research divisions. They were created for Time Inc. sales staff, advertising sales representatives, advertisers, magazine readers and subscribers. While the advertising promotion and circulation promotion departments were separate within the Time Inc. structure, their files were collected together in order to demonstrate the full scope of a magazine's revenue generating activities.
Materials present throughout the record group include correspondence, memoranda, print advertisements, displays, mailings, magazines, books and booklets, reprints, reports, studies, promotional memorabilia, and audio recordings. There are also scrapbooks and binders of files collected by year. Dates range from 1922 Time pre-publication files to 2004 Fortune 500 playing cards, although the bulk of files fall between 1923 and 1989. The files are arranged by magazine title and further organized by subject, generally grouped into Advertisers Lists, Advertising Promotion, and Circulation Promotion.
Time Inc. magazine titles consist of Discover, Fortune, Fortune International, Life, Life International, Money, People, President, Sports Illustrated, Time, Time Canada, Time International, and TV-Cable Week. Life International files also contain Life En Español, a Spanish-language edition for the Latin American market. Time International files encompass Time Asia, Time Atlantic, Time Latin America, and Time Pacific editions, as well as some Time Canada materials. President is a Japanese business magazine that was established in 1963 as a partner magazine to Fortune. Other Time Inc. topics in the collection include book clubs, CompuServe, and HBO/Cinemax.
Advertisers Lists are records of the magazines' advertising sales, organized chronologically by year or issue. In addition to listing all advertisers, they may contain breakdowns of advertising page counts, advertising dollar amounts, and advertising categories. These reports both document the advertising activities of the past and demonstrate trends over time. They were used by Time Inc. to measure growth and decline across years and categories, as well as for comparison against competing magazines. Advertisers Lists files are present for Fortune, Life, Life International, and Time International magazines.
Advertising Promotion files document the company's efforts to attract and retain advertisers and sell advertising space in its magazines. There is a large collection of Time Inc. advertisements, including self-promotional house ads for the company's other publications, trade ads for industry trade journals, general print ads for newspapers and consumer magazines, bound inserts and wrap-around outserts, and posters and displays for retailers of products advertised by Time Inc. It contains proofs and clippings, and sizes range from small space ads to large fold-outs and window displays. Promotional mailings were distributed to advertising sales representatives and potential clients to demonstrate the benefits of advertising with Time Inc. magazines. Examples include advertising reports, calendars, Christmas cards and small gifts (such as paper ornaments or garland), holiday gift advertising and buying guides, media kits, newsletters, promotional booklets, reprints of articles and photographs, special magazine issues, and Time Inc. memorabilia, books and commemorative gifts, as well as general direct mail. Time Inc. conducted extensive market research to analyze their magazines' advertising effectiveness, and findings reports were often used in promotional materials. Market research materials include studies by Time Inc. or external research services (such as Alfred Politz and Elmo Roper), readership surveys, subscriber lists, and samples and directories of prominent subscribers within certain companies, industries or areas, as well as celebrities and politicians. Finally, there are records from company's various advertising promotion departments, including internal staff memoranda discussing marketing strategies, memoranda to sales representatives, manuals, price lists of advertising rates, ad specifications, sales convention souvenir booklets and memorabilia, speeches, and presentation materials. Advertising Promotion files are present for Fortune, Fortune International, Life, Life International, Money, People, President, Sports Illustrated, Time, Time International, and TV-Cable Week magazines, as well as HBO/Cinemax.
Circulation Promotion files focus on increasing Time Inc. magazine circulation and subscriptions. Promotional efforts targeted existing and potential subscribers. These files contain advertisements geared towards consumers, including house ads for Time Inc. publications, subscription card inserts, promotional tip-ons such as coupons, newsstand banners, and retailer displays. The bulk of the collection is mailings to magazine readers and subscribers. Examples include acknowledgements thanking new subscribers, billings, Christmas gift subscriptions, direct mail offers, promotional gifts, renewal notices and reminders, and sweepstakes. Miniature Time Inc. branded pencils were commonly included for recipients' use. Other mailings include discontinued magazine subscription transfers and notices of Life's suspension of publication in 1972. There are also cooperative mailing campaigns with department stores, which promoted magazine subscriptions to customers. Finally, the company's various circulation departments' records include staff memoranda, promotional budget breakdowns and worksheets, renewal price rates, and mailing test results and statistics. Circulation Promotion files are present for Discover, Fortune, Life, Life International, Money, People, Sports Illustrated, Time, Time Canada, Time International, and TV-Cable Week magazines.
Additionally, the record group contains Time Education Department files, a division of the magazine's Circulation Department under Director of Education Mary Tweedy. It features College Bureau, a college subscription sales program based in campus bookstores and sold by student representatives at special student and educator rates. Materials include correspondence, memoranda, information kits, promotional displays, signs and banners, subscription order cards, and awards for high sales. The files also contain educational materials for elementary, high school and college students based on Time articles and editorials. Examples include magazine cover quizzes, current affairs tests, special classroom magazine editions, and teaching aid packets on topics such as nuclear power, electoral politics, and Islam.
Corporations -- History.; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Corporation records.; Organization files.; Advertising -- Periodicals; Advertising, Direct-mail -- Periodicals; Advertising, Magazine; Marketing research; Periodicals -- Circulation; Advertisements.; Books; Direct mail; Magazines (periodicals).; Newsletters.; Press kits.; Press releases.; Promotional materials.; Souvenir programs.; Subscription lists; Time, inc. -- Archives.; Time, inc. -- History.
- Archives storage labels, 1995 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 1a)
- Book Clubs: The Book Find Club/Seven Arts Society Promotion, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 1b)
- Book Clubs: Fortune Book Club Promotion, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 2)
- Book Clubs: Sports Illustrated Book Club Promotion, 1973 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 3)
- Book Clubs: Miscellaneous Promotion, circa 1973 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 4)
- Circulation Promotion Samples Inventory (All magazines except Life), 1980 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 5)
- CompuServe [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Offsite-box R55, Folder 49)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes digital material. 1 computer disc (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in.
- Discover: Circulation Promotion: Direct Mail Tests, 1980 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 6)
- Discover: Circulation Promotion: Inhouse, 1980 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 7)
- Fortune: Advertisers Lists: General, 1930-1952, 1955-1966 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 8-17)
- Fortune: Advertisers Lists: Agencies, 1930-1952 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 18-19)
- Fortune: Advertisers Lists: Exclusive, 1936-1952 (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 20)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1929-1930: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1930-1934: General (Offsite-box 3453, Folder 21)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1930-1934: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 1-3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1930-1934: Promotion Booklets (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1931-1935: House Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1931-1935: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 4-5)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1931-1935: Trade Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 6-8)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1935-1939: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 4-7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1935-1939: Promotion Booklets (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1936: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1937: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1940: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 8)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Promotion Booklets (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1941: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3455, Folder 16)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Promotion Booklets (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 1-2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1942: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1943-1944: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Promotion Booklets (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 5)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 6)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1945: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1945: "The Story of a Fortune Story", circa 1945 (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1946: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 8)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Promotion Booklets (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1947: General (Offsite-box 3454, Folder 15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1947: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Promotion Booklets (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 11-12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1948-1949: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3456, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1950: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1951: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1952: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 5-8)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1952: General (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1952: "How to Read Fortune in Bed" (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 9-10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1953: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1953: General (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 5)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 6)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1954: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 12-13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1954: General (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1954: House Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 8)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1955: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 14-15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1955: General (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1955: House Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1956: General (Offsite-box 3457, Folder 16)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1956: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1956: General (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Trade Paper Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1957: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1957: General (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 16-17)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1957: "How to Measure a Magazine's Readership" (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 3-4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3458, Folder 18)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1958: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 5-6)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1958: General (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1959: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 7-9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1960: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 10-12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1960: General (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 4-6)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1961: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1961: General (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 8-9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1961-1962: Print Ads: "Concentration" (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1962: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1962: General (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1962: "Fortune Fact File" (Offsite-box 3459, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1962-1964: Print Ads: "Back to Back" (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1963: General (Offsite-box 3460, Folder 15-16)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1963: General (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "The Financial Analyst" (Offsite-box 3461, Folder 1-2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1964: General (Offsite-box 3461, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1964: General (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 5)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 6)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1965: General (Offsite-box 3461, Folder 4-5)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1965: General (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 7-8)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1965-1966: Print Ads: "Quote" Campaign (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1966: General (Offsite-box 3461, Folder 6-7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1966: General (Offsite-box 3462, Folder 11-14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Fortune's Input/Output Portfolio (Offsite-box 3463, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Letters Binder, circa 1966 (Offsite-box 3463, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Print Ads (Offsite-box 3463, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: General (Offsite-box 3461, Folder 8-12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: General (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 1)
  Includes graphic material. 3 color slides in film canisters. Handwritten on labels: "F.F. [Fortune Forum]"
  Formerly housed in cardboard enclosure with label: "Corp. Pres. Record returned from Mike Goul - Phila - 8/23/67."
  Separated from 3 phonograph records.
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: General (Offsite-box 3463, Folder 4-6)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: General (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 1)
  Includes audiovisual material.
  1 phonograph record (33 1/3 rpm); 12 in. On label: "Side A 6/27/67. A Fortune Forum. Corporate Advertising. Dukane automatic signal. Focus 1st. frame, advance to black and start record."
  1 phonograph records (33 1/3 rpm); 12 in. (2 copies); On label: "A Fortune Forum. Corporate Advertising. Focus on focus frame. Advance to black & start record."
  Records formerly housed in cardboard enclosure. Retained label: "Corp. Pres. Record returned from Mike Goul - Phila - 8/23/67." Separated from 3 color slide canisters.
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Annotated Issue (Offsite-box 3463, Folder 7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: "Before and After Studies" (Offsite-box 3463, Folder 8-9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: California Conference, 1967 May (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: "Fortune and Business Publications" (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1967: "Sales Letters to be used for the Financial Classification" (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1968: General (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 4-7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1968: General (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Campaign #68125 (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 8)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Ponte Vedra Conference (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 9-10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1968-1969: Print Ads: "Big F" (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1969: General (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Campaign #691-6960 (Offsite-box 3465, Folder 12-15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Campaign #6961-69240 (Offsite-box 3466, Folder 1-16)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Campaign #69241-69440 (Offsite-box 3467, Folder 1-16)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Campaign #69441-69491 (Offsite-box 3468, Folder 1-3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Campaign #7041-70220 (Offsite-box 3468, Folder 4-15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Campaign #70221-70440 (Offsite-box 3469, Folder 1-14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Campaign #711-71200 (Offsite-box 3470, Folder 1-14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Campaign #71201-71413 (Offsite-box 3471, Folder 1-14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Campaign #71414-71440 (Offsite-box 3472, Folder 1-3)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Campaign #721-72160 (Offsite-box 3472, Folder 4-12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Campaign #72161-72420 (Offsite-box 3473, Folder 1-16)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Campaign #72421-72520 (Offsite-box 3474, Folder 1-7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1973: Campaign #731-7380 (Offsite-box 3474, Folder 8-13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1973: Campaign #7381-73280 (Offsite-box 3475, Folder 1-14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1973: Campaign #73281-73480 (Offsite-box 3476, Folder 1-14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1974: Campaign #741-74280 (Offsite-box 3477, Folder 1-15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1974: Campaign #74261-74380 (Offsite-box 3478, Folder 1-14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1975-1981: Reprints (Offsite-box 3479, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1977: General (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 5)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1978: General (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 6)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1978: Reprints (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1979: General (Offsite-box 3479, Folder 2-4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1980: General (Offsite-box 3479, Folder 5-8)
  Includes Fortune-branded ceramic coaster.
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Fortune Magazine. 1. United Technologies :60 Radio."
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1980: General, 1980 September (Offsite-box 3479, Folder 9-10)
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "B-377. Fortune Magazine. 1. Money Supply :60."
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1980: General, 1980 October-December (Offsite-box 3479, Folder 11-13)